

Alexandr Melnic

Full Stack Web Developer < MERN Tech Stack />

Highly motivated and curious. (In my previous Job position, was fast promoted and assigned special tasks),
 Well structured and a good team player. (our team won 2nd place at our local Hackathon for the project structure and good timing)
 Experienced and fast Google Searcher. (always found a suitable solution for my problem)

☑ Email

in /https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandr-melnic-43177a6b

Phone number

github.com/AlexandrMel

WORK EXPERIENCE

Student at Full Stack Web Development Ausbildung

DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH Full-time

Mar / 2019 - Present / yyyy

Berlin Area, Germany

Achivements / Tasks

- 1. HTML, CSS & SCSS, Bootstrap 2. JavaScript & jQuery 3.
 Git & Version Control 4. React 5. Node.js & Express 6. SQLite
 & MangoDB 7. Testing & Deployment 8. Project
 Management

Data Entry Operator

AutoDoc

Nov / 2016 - Nov / 2018
Achivements / Tasks

Berlin Area, Germany

 Main Highlights Improved my typing speed; Improved my attention to details; Worked in a big team; Improved my Time Management skills. see less

HR Manager

Grawe Carat Asigurări S.A.

Jun / 2013 - Nov / 2016 Achivements / Tasks Chisinau

 Main Highlights Improved my Communication skills;
 International working environment; Improved my critical thinking; Improved my organizational skills; Directed the implementation of new HR software in the company; Was promoted from Junior HR to HR Manager in 1 year. see less

HR Junior

Grawe Carat Asigurări S.A.

Mar / 2012 - Jun / 2013 Achivements / Tasks Chisinau, Moldova

- Accomplishment/Responsability/Task

EDUCATION

AusbildungWeb Development

DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH

mm / 2019 - mm / 2020

City, Country

SKILLS

Node.js MongoDB React.js Performance Management **Human Resources** HTML5 Agile Project Management CSS3 JavaScript SASS jQuery **Employee Relations Team Management Organizational Development** Training Time Management **Critical Thinking** Structural Thinking **Creativity Skills** Vanila Javascript Flexibility Bootstrapping Express.js **Git & Version Control Puppeteering**

PROJECTS

Project name

Description of achievements

CERTIFICATIONS

Certificate name

ACHIEVEMENTS

Achievement name

COURSES

The Web Developer Bootcamp by Colt Steele on Udemy.com

Description

LANGUAGES

Language name English Professional working proficiency Language name German Elementary proficiency

Bi

Master Degree in Lahor Lawl abor Law

WORK EXPERIENCE

Procurement Contract Specialist

Camargo Corrêa

Jan / 2007 - Apr / 2012

São Paulo e Região, Brasil

Achivements / Tasks

- During 5 years of work on this Brazilian multinational company, I was involved in 3 major projects: 2010 to 2012 – International Expediter Lead and Contract Management Project: RNEST (Energy Transmission line Construction) Client: PETROBRAS Hightlight: RNEST Project became the most modern refinery that Petrobras ever built, RNEST will also be the 5th largest unit in refining capacity (230,000 barrels per day - bpd). I worked for 3 years in this project as the International Expediter Lead, performing monthly expediting visits at supplier shops all around the world in order to ensure the contract terms. Oil & Gas 2009 to 2010 -Procurement Coordinator Project: UÍGE (Energy Transmission line Construction) Client: ANGOLA GOVERNMENT Infrastructure 2007 to 2009 – Procurement Analyst Project: ALUMAR (Alluminium Refinery Expansion) Client: ALCOA Light Metals see less

EDUCATION

Degree in LawCivil Law

Universitatea de Stat din Moldova

mm / 2007 - mm / 2011

City, Country

baccalaureate degreeGeneral Field

National Liceum "Mihai Viteazul"

mm / 1995 - mm / 2007

City, Country

WeiterbildungFull Stack Web Development

DCI Digital Career Institute GmbH

mm / 2019 - mm / 2020

City, Country

Engineer's degreeProduction Engineering Unifass

mm / 2009 - mm / 2014

City, Country

Business and Professional English

The London School of English

mm / 2005 - mm / 2006

City, Country

BachareladoPublicidade, Propaganda e Marketing

Universidade Presbiteriana Mackenzie

mm / 2000 - mm / 2004

City, Country

PROJECTS

UFN3 Petrobras Project

Project description UFN III Project consists in a
Nitrogen Fertilizing Plant construction, in Três Lagoas
City, MT, Brazil. This Project target was to improve
production of Ammonia and Ureia to be used mainly
for Agriculture purposes. My main role on this project
was to coordinate the expediting and inspection team
inside Procurement department.

RNEST Petrobras Project

Project description RNEST Project became the most modern refinery that Petrobras ever built, RNEST will also be the 5th largest unit in refining capacity (230,000 barrels per day - bpd). I collaborated in this project as the International Expediter Lead, performing monthly expediting visits at supplier shops all around the world in order to ensure the contract terms.

Uige - Maquela do Zombo

Project description This project was a construction of a energy transmission line of 200km between cities

Uige and Maquela do Zombo in Angola. According to a agreement with BNDES all equipments and materials were exported by brazilian suppliers. My main role on this project was to expedite and inspect equipments and materials before shipping to Angola.

Alumar - ALREFU2 - Alumina Refinery Expansion II

Project description ALREFU2 is an plant expansion of existing Alumar refinery in São Luis do Maranhão. This USD 3,0 Billions CAPEX project was a complex design made in two different countries (Brazil and Australia) using different system tools such as PDS, SmartPlant Instrumentation, SmartPlant Materials and I-sketch.

CERTIFICATIONS

Certificate name

ACHIEVEMENTS

Achievement name

COURSES

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp (Codecademy)

Description

PMI - Project Management (Corporative

LANGUAGES

Language name Romanian Language name Russian

Native or bilingual Native or bilingual

proficiency proficiency

B1 B1

English German

81 81

Portuguese Spanish

81 81